(A total of 10 charming older women and younger men...)
(have come to the Yeon House in search of love.)
(Gu Ji Seung)
(Park Ji Hye)
(Choi Yu Jin)
(Yu Ju Hee)
(Lee Si Won)
(Lee Jun Han)
(Yu Jin Wu)
(Lee Yun So)
(Lee Jin Young)
(Kim Jeong Won)
(They only had love in their eyes...)
(during the 7 days in the Yeon House.)
(I just wanted to take care of you.)
(I wish for you not to cry.)
(The final decision to check each other's hearts)
Okay.
(Ju Hee and Yun So with an 11-year age gap)
(Ji Hye and Jeong Won with a 6-year age gap)
(Jin Young and Jin Wu with a 1-year age gap)
(Three months later after leaving the Yeon House)
(A studio in Seoul)
(The empty seats haven't been filled yet.)
(Out of the older women and younger men, who will come first?)
It looks nice.
(Laughing)
(Ju Hee and Yun So arrive first.)
Is this right?
- Where's our seat?
- Is this it?
I'm not sure.
- We're here first.
- Right.
(It's great to see Ju Hee and Yun So,)
(the couple with an 11-year age gap.)
(Peeking)
(The two put on a smile just by looking at each other.)
I feel nervous as it has been quite a while.
Shouldn't we be talking?
(It's been a while since we've seen Ju Hee's trademark dimple.)
Right.
Gosh.
Can I help take off your hair for you?
Yes. Is my hair stuck?
Done.
I came with an unfamiliar hairstyle.
It looks nice.
(Smiling)
- Oh!
- Hi!
(The second couple we're glad to see, Ji Hye and Jeong Won)
(Hugging out of delight)
- You came in right away.
- Did you do well?
- You look so handsome.
- You look great.
You look prettier.
- Gosh.
- You look prettier.
I thought you were a celebrity.
(Ji Hye and Jeong Won still look great together...)
(as a couple with a 6-year age gap.)
It feels like it was yesterday since we've seen each other.
- Right.
- Time flies.
You two look even better together outside.
- The same goes for the two of you.
- Really?
I'm still better than him.
You haven't changed.
- This is our love, isn't it?
- Of course.
It feels like we're in the Yeon House.
- I want to go back.
- Right.
It was great fun.
I cried because I wanted to go back home.
(I cried because I wanted to go back home.)
Those moments became memories now.
It was really tough back then.
Right.
I wanted to go home when I was there. But now, I want to go back.
Will you choose me again if we go back?
(I don't know.)
- Hello!
- Hey!
- It's been a while.
- Hi!
(They're holding hands as they come in.)
- It's been a while.
- Hello!
- Did you all do well?
- You look great!
(Jin Wu and Jin Young come in holding hands.)
Why are you sitting so far away?
- What?
- We wanted this seat.
- Well...
It's to protect her.
That's why we're going to sit away.
(Keeping a good distance from Jeong Won)
Gosh.
I'm sorry.
(Feeling cute about him)
That's why we're going to sit away.
(Relieved)
- Are things going well for you two?
- Well,
we would die without each other.
(Laughing)
We see each other almost every day.
You all look like celebrities.
No.
You look the best.
(Failing to hold their laughter)
Make sure to wet your lips.
You do look great.
I saw you through the show...
and you stared at me so much, Yun So.
I stared at Jun Han a lot more than I stared at you.
(Unable to deny it)
I didn't stare at you that much.
(You're right.)
- Hello.
- Oh, Jun Han's here!
(Jun Han appears at that moment.)
The one with the great physique.
Hi!
Did you do well?
I did do well.
Your body looks even bigger.
(He still has his baby smile although he is bigger.)
All I can see is his nose.
What kind of response did you get at home?
My parents...
enjoyed it.
They found it funny.
My family put up a banner...
for being on public television.
- Really?
- My family put up a banner.
Really?
No.
How could that be true?
I thought it was true.
- Your outfit looks nice.
- What?
Your outfit looks nice.
Are you a celebrity today?
I like tone-on-tone outfits.
You look great all the time.
(Lovey-dovey)
(Couple 1, Couple 2, Couple 3)
Are you a celebrity today?
It's great to see all of you together.
It's a pretty sight.
- Hey, guys.
- Yu Jin!
Yu Jin!
(She changes the atmosphere by making a wave.)
She's giving everyone a high-five.
I love the wave.
- You're sitting there...
- Gosh.
all on your own.
(Awkward)
I feel lonely on my own.
Right. Same here.
(I waited for you.)
Hello!
- Si Won!
- Our handsome one.
- It's been a while.
- Did you do well, Si Won?
(Si Won greets Yu Jin first.)
- Si Won looks amazing.
- Si Won is handsome.
- He looks amazing.
- It's been a while.
- He looks even better.
- Right.
- Si Won is handsome.
(Looking intently)
(Smiling)_
I'm on a remote island on my own.
Where's Ji Seung?
(Jun Han!)
She said she was at work...
- and couldn't make it.
- She's on a business trip.
It's disappointing she couldn't come.
- Right.
- Everyone is working hard.
It's great to see everyone after a while like this.
- Right.
This place feels like the common area.
I want to go back!
She said she wouldn't have picked me if she had gone back.
(Laughing)
I wouldn't have picked you.
Then, who would you have picked?
Who would you have picked?
Could it have been Jin Wu?
Jin Wu is too much for me.
(Relieved)
Gosh, what?
How can you say that?
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry, Jin Wu.)
Has there been another show...
that has brought together this many actual couples?
Everyone around me got surprised...
after hearing we became an actual couple.
Right.
Are you two doing well?
Our love for each other is extremely hot.
- It's hot.
Right.
(Ji Hye and Jeong Won's love for each other is hot.)
As soon as we left the Yeon House,
we had so much piled-up work to take care of.
We were busy taking care of our work.
We worked hard and loved hard.
We worked passionately and loved passionately.
Do you two meet each other often?
- We meet each other a lot.
- Do you think so?
We meet each other really often at this age.
"At this age."
- With a guy in his 20s...
- What's wrong with your age?
- You're right about that.
- Right.
We're seeing each other with passion.
Right.
We see each other every day.
(You're right.)
What about the two of you?
Are you two not passionate?
- Us?
- Are you talking about us?
Yes.
We're dating each other like high schoolers.
What does that mean?
We have nicknames for each other.
What are your nicknames?
Princess!
(Embarrassed)
(This can't be true.)
It feels upsetting if you respond like this after asking for it.
Does Jin Young call you Prince?
Are you Prince?
Noona? She calls me like that only when she feels like it.
Do you call her noona?
Yes. I call her noona.
I tell him...
not to call me by my name.
Really?
You really tighten the reins.
We're only nine months apart,
but I really want to hear him call me noona.
That's something you can hear when the guy is younger.
It's my first time meeting a younger guy,
so I want to hear him call me noona.
It's cute sometimes when you hear him call you noona, right?
- He's cute all the time.
- Gosh.
He's cute all the time.
(Jin Young's cute younger guy, Jin Wu)
Call me noona too.
Why bother?
You're my honey.
My lady.
(Laughing)
Gosh, Si Won!
Yes?
- It's hard to be here.
- Right.
Yun So and Ju Hee, we want to hear from the two of you as well.
- Us?
- Yes.
We're doing well together.
My days off...
and her days off don't match.
- I see.
- We're really...
trying our best to find time to see each other.
You two must go on dates often during your spare time.
My work schedule changed.
It's a huge bummer that none of our days off match.
- Yun So's days off are weekdays.
- Right.
But a schedule change...
can be made for at least one day a week.
Since that was possible,
we decided to...
tell each other in advance.
But I'm a perceiver.
(I understand.)
- I'm a judger.
- I'm a spontaneous person.
I should be the one to tell him in advance,
but I struggle to do that.
(That's hilarious.)
He can't make it if I tell him all of a sudden.
I don't tend to go if she tells me all of a sudden.
He won't come out?
- Right.
- He won't come out.
Well,
I plan my whole day out in advance.
You're a total planner.
- It's great that...
- He has his own routines.
he has his own routines.
It's great to see him live like that,
but I still want him to come out.
- Right.
Girls feel a bit upset when the guy doesn't come.
I still want him to come out,
but he's really strict when it comes to those things.
But you're seeing a younger guy for that reason.
You're meeting a younger guy to be in a passionate love.
That's what we can feel by dating a younger guy.
Yun So feels different compared to when he was in the Yeon House.
He has changed a bit.
You said you could give her your liver.
He said he could give me his liver.
- Give me what?
- Should I give you my liver?
- Are you joking?
- No.
- I'm serious.
- You're being serious?
I can give you my liver.
- Really?
- Yes.
Are you still willing to give her your liver?
(I already gave it to her.)
You already gave it to her, right?
I don't have it as I already gave it to her.
Are you not going out to see her as you already gave it to her?
What? That's not it.
"I have you now."
That's not it!
- You should go before she calls.
- Right.
You have to be there before she says she misses you.
You should say, "I came to see you because I missed you."
If a younger guy tells me that...
- he'll give me his liver...
- I'll give you my liver.
- Gosh!
- Gosh, Si Won!
Gosh, Si Won!
(Heart fluttering)
Should we head back to the Yeon House?
- I should've said this earlier.
- Gosh.
I would've picked you if you had said that.
- Really?
- Yes.
I should've learned a lot from Yun So.
- You gave me supplements instead.
- Right.
- I thought supplements were enough.
- You have to give your liver.
- You have to use your liver.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- This is tough.
- Right.
- What about you, Jin Wu?
- What?
I can give you my kidney.
You can even give up your kidney?
- My kidney and cornea.
- Right.
I can give you all of those things.
(Feeling happy)
What can you give me?
Take everything you need.
Come in.
- Take everything you need.
- Gosh!
It makes my blood boil whenever he's like this.
(Acting cute)
That's hilarious.
(Watching the trending clips)
(Catfish Jin Young's entrance scene got everyone's attention.)
- The catfish.
- Gosh.
There are more than 4.34 million views.
- That's amazing.
- It's the second most viewed...
- in the streaming channel.
- I'm jealous, Jin Wu.
(I believe I'm an all-rounder.)
There aren't any flaws with my brain, character,
and appearance.
I've already purchased a house...
- in a good location.
- I'm really jealous.
That was impressive.
"Just come and do the house chores."
- "I'll bring home the bacon." - I wanted to meet her.
(Impressed)
She really is doing that.
I think I can pay for his student loans.
But personal loans...
are a no for me.
I said that with a genuine heart.
Even if Jin Wu doesn't do anything...
and wishes to get married to me,
I can provide for him.
I'm sure Jin Wu won't be like that in reality.
You all must come to our wedding.
You all must come.
I have a question, Jin Young.
Do you have any debt?
(I'm quite curious.)
Jin Wu keeps telling me...
he wants to marry me.
Oh, that's great.
- There's a reason.
- He tells me every day...
that he wants to marry me.
I watched Jin Wu's interview.
He said he was ready to get married...
and live with someone.
"I'll take care of you, Jin Wu."
- How nice.
- That's cool.
You've all heard her, right?
A verbal agreement is still an agreement.
(The first time Jin Wu saw Jin Young)
(Exclaiming)
- Hello.
- Jin Wu fell for her.
He fell for her. That's when he fell for her.
He had already fallen for her then.
It's so obvious that you've fallen for her.
(Laughing)
(He did fall for her.)
- Get it together, Jin Wu!
- "Get it together, Jin Wu."
(Get it together, Jin Wu.)
(How cute)
Hey, get it together!
- Jun Han...
- Jun Han has fallen for her too.
I had fallen for her.
(He immediately admits it.)
But you went out on a date with me.
Your type is basically any girl you see for the first time, right?
Yes. I like women I'm meeting for the first time.
(Jun Han's first dates were Jin Young and Yu Jin.)
(I'm just joking.)
(An exciting comments section was prepared today.)
"Hello, my name is Baek Jong Ho."
"Can it be someone who's already married?"
There were about 200 or 300 of such comments.
- That's right.
- This isn't the only channel...
that the clip was uploaded.
You could see it on many different channels.
I read all the comments there.
Was there a comment that really stuck with you?
A comment that really stuck with me?
Someone said he'd wash my feet every day.
That he'd wash my feet every evening.
My neck.
After reading that, I said,
"You better be nervous, Jin Wu."
Jin Wu should be nervous.
Start filling a basin with water every day, Jin Wu.
I told him, "What are you going to do now?"
- Are you going to be swayed?
- Well...
- Of course not.
- Then I won't mind.
- You're the only one.
- I won't get nervous.
There's something I thought was very impressive.
I was touched.
We recently went to Jeju on a trip.
Jin Wu got very sick.
It suddenly happened around 9pm.
His fever rose to about 38°C.
So... But there wasn't any pharmacy open nearby.
I drove for an hour in the rain...
to get some medicine for him.
- That's touching.
- She's so cool.
That time, Jin Wu...
suddenly hugged me...
and said this in tears.
"If I marry you someday,"
"it will be because of this moment."
Really?
(Feeling cringy)
That was really moving for me. It was touching.
They're filming a whole movie.
It's like a K-drama for us.
(They're emotionally compatible.)
(They look good together.)
The next clip.
(What's the second trending clip?)
That got 3.8 million views?
- That's a lot.
- It got a lot of views.
I guess you were really excited then.
That time, you...
I was really excited.
(She won't say any further.)
Do you like wearing matching outfits?
I do.
- I also do.
- He likes everything.
(Jun Han is overflowing with butterflies.)
You were that excited. You're really...
- How could you?
- I was happy.
I told her we should wear matching outfits today as well.
That's the cute charm of a younger man.
- That's right.
- Getting so excited about going...
- Right.
- on a date with an older woman.
I think that was the cute part of that scene.
That's right.
You two are the type...
that makes us want to root for.
My family really loved Jun Han so much.
"Jun Han is such a fine guy."
They said we looked good together, and asked me, "Is it that guy?"
My parents liked you as well.
(Laughing)
Maybe you should try again now.
I'll send you the QR code again.
Can you wear matching outfits?
Are you going to commit to her?
I'm sorry. Jin Young is here as well.
- There's Ji Hye as well.
- Hold on.
All four of them are here now.
- That's true. We're all here.
- All four of us are here.
I'm sorry.
(All the 4 women who showed interest in Jun Han are here.)
Anyway, he was really cute there.
That's right. The way...
- he went running over was cute.
- That's right.
I was really excited then.
(1.48 million views)
(Crying)
What am I going to do?
(Sighing)
I find this really funny.
His reaction was too real.
(He got a chance to check the photo in the Secret Room.)
Your reaction was so funny.
That photo of her looks so old.
It's such an old picture.
Seriously.
- You look cute.
- There were many other pictures.
(Looking confused)
In 2006?
(Scratching)
Was Yun So five years old then? Four?
Don't be like that.
(Smiling)
In 2006...
(Impersonating himself)
She was this old already?
It's so funny.
The comments on this were really funny.
That's right.
"He's subtly rude."
That's really...
"Subtly rude" is so funny.
Why did you suddenly switch to super-formal speech?
I wasn't about to say in super-formal speech...
I could calculate the numbers, you know.
Did you use super-formal speech without even realizing?
I didn't even know I said that.
I knew from watching this.
- It was a genuine reaction.
- It was a genuine vibe.
(A genuine vibe?)
So, after watching this...
That's why you used super-formal speech?
Right.
That was also funny.
You kept looking up.
- Exactly.
- With empty eyes.
He was counting the numbers.
Born in 2004?
I kept calculating while looking up.
Yun So really has a melancholic vibe.
(Feeling embarrassed)
He always looks at the ceiling when he's thinking.
That's right.
You'd have guessed her age back then.
Did you still like her the same way?
Right. I could get an idea...
- from that picture.
- Right.
But it didn't matter to me.
- That was the first day, right?
- Right.
On the first day, you saw her, and...
I think it was love at first sight.
All right.
(Ju Hee and Yun So with an age gap of 11 years)
(Ju Hee and Yun So's first date)
Ju Hee was so pretty that day.
This place looks really nice.
- Right.
- Isn't it?
(Staring)
I looked at her from the side. She was beautiful.
- She looks pretty.
- I felt that...
for the first time in a while. It felt new.
You can see the love in his eyes.
I should have stuck with him starting from that time.
That's right.
- I thought about Ju Hee a lot.
- Right.
(I thought about Ju Hee a lot during the date.)
That's pure love.
What do you like about Ju Hee?
I've started to get a bit curious.
I heard him talk all day.
I think I know Ju Hee well now.
I'm sorry.
She's just...
I think the best word to describe her is a fairy.
(Feeling embarrassed)
I also think this part of Ju Hee is amazing.
What part?
I publicly said...
that I like her.
But even after that,
she still approaches people who she's interested in.
I think that also requires a lot of courage.
Yes, that's not easy to do.
I really like that she's true to herself.
I'm upset. I'm hurt too.
- But...
- That's cute.
- I think that's...
her strength and charm.
He's head over heels for her.
Does she still seem like a fairy to you?
A fairy?
She looks better every time I see her.
She dyed her hair recently...
and became so pretty.
- This is like a drama.
- Seriously.
(My roommate hasn't changed.)
- Learn from him.
- You haven't changed.
Why are you scolding me?
I saw his eyes. He's serious.
- I'm serious.
- He's serious.
- He means it.
- I tell her every day.
How do you feel when you hear that you're like a fairy?
It feels nice.
- It's nice.
- Nice. I'm glad you two met.
(I like it too.)
I really can't make a guess.
(The age reveal day, when reality could become an issue)
I'll say 2000.
I was born in...
two thousand...
- Two thousand?
Her eyes became so big.
three.
(Born in 2003, 24 years old)
It looks like she really had no clue.
You were the youngest?
He's 24 years old.
I was quite flustered...
when I heard his age.
Since I want to meet someone...
who I can build a future with,
profession and age matter quite a lot.
You can't ignore those.
You're all so young.
- The average suddenly dropped.
- It suddenly dropped.
Well,
- we have an age gap, - Yes.
and it's not necessarily a burden,
but I think there are things you wouldn't have thought about.
So I can't bring them up.
So I'd rather you...
be more curious about me.
It's also hard...
- Why?
- for me to talk to you because...
Yes?
It feels like...
I'm more focused on dating,
- and you...
- Right.
seem more focused...
on getting married.
- That's not entirely wrong.
- Right.
You're half right.
I haven't thought about that...
so seriously yet.
I thought so too.
That's why I can't ask you about it.
That's why I'm also scared to ask you things.
(Their focus about dating and marriage is different.)
It can't be helped because you're in different age groups.
Your focus would be different.
Like Ju Hee said, when you talked about marriage...
Actually, we also know...
that getting married is difficult.
But if you had just said,
"I'll prepare for it well, Ju Hee,"
it would have been...
a little...
easier for Ju Hee to decide quickly.
To speak from Yun So's perspective...
I've been his age before too.
If I think about how I was at that age,
I can understand what he said.
At his age, it's only natural...
that dating is his main focus.
I was telling him...
- the situation I was in.
- Right.
I wasn't suggesting us to do anything.
I said that to explain my situation...
so he could take it...
more seriously.
But that...
(I know.)
Of course, it could feel like a burden to him.
He may not have wanted to say empty words.
I think that's the right way to put it.
In the end, if I was to continue this relationship,
there were some things I had to take care of.
I didn't want to say that...
- so lightly.
- Right.
I think that's why I gave an unrelated answer.
I was flustered as well.
- I think that's understandable.
- Right.
How is it now? Have you figured things out?
We're talking about so many things.
For now, we're just focusing on each other.
I think she was being considerate by suggesting...
that we focus on the present rather than the future.
(7 days later, the day of the final decision)
You met her at the Han River.
(Yun So arrived at the meeting place first.)
(The two had the most realistic concerns.)
What?
How pretty.
(He fell for her again.)
He fell in love again.
How many times will you fall for her?
She looks beautiful.
- Mine's so small.
- That's right.
I asked them to make it small...
Right.
Even his flowers are younger.
- The size?
- The size.
I thought it was my graduation.
That's cute.
I have a question.
What is it?
Did you tell your parents?
I told them right away.
You told them right away?
- Yes.
- I was so worried about that.
Right. I get why.
(She was worried how his parents would react.)
Actually, it was just...
as I expected.
"We respect your decision."
"We don't mind whether she's 11 years or 20 years older."
Twenty years?
My parents said they respect my decision.
Did you tell your parents?
To some extent...
(Hesitating)
- You were careful.
- I told them to some extent.
I feel like you'd feel more burdened.
The age...
I'm confident I can handle it.
I think I could learn a lot from you regarding this.
I'm excited about our future together.
(Looking into her eyes)
I told my mom.
But I couldn't tell my dad.
Dad got to know now.
(She's shocked.)
What did your mom say?
Mom...
is worried. She's still worried.
Right.
Dad just found out a few days ago.
The day before yesterday.
(Feeling surprised)
Are you okay, Yun So?
I think that's also part of what I have to deal with.
You should get through it if you're a man.
You should.
(That's right.)
What about you two?
How is it?
My dad supports us.
He supports us.
I think it's a relief.
I didn't tell them until the end.
I didn't tell my parents who the final couple was.
Even to your parents?
I didn't tell them,
so every Wednesday, my parents would say,
"Will it be Jin Young or Ji Hye?"
They said they were excited.
(It's me, Mother.)
They were like that.
I actually told my mom...
who the real couples were.
She watched the show and suddenly said,
"Didn't you say Jeong Won was with Ji Hye?"
Even Jeong Won's parents are confused.
My mom is confused.
She called him.
She kept calling me during the show.
Did she say, "Who did you end up with?"
"What are you doing?"
Seriously.
What about you? Did you tell your parents?
Jin Wu met my mom.
(Exclaiming)
- Already?
- Yes.
The hospital... My parents are in Cheongju.
Jin Wu came to Cheongju,
and we happened to run into each other.
So we talked.
Mom really likes Jin Wu.
Really?
- He's so polite.
- Right.
She really likes him.
My parents are like Jeong Won's parents.
Before she came,
there were four women.
"There's no one called Jin Young among the four."
"Who is she?"
So I didn't tell her yet.
She got to know after she appeared.
I see.
My parents like her...
because she's pretty.
Seriously. This is so annoying.
Right.
Yes.
While watching the show, I was a little...
- worried...
- Right.
about these two couples.
At first,
- So...
- you were matched differently.
(Shaking her head)
(Goodness)
We both didn't know...
how each other's date went.
I didn't know how he was like with the other person.
When I watched the show... From the back, he...
From the back...
(From the back)
Honey.
You said you were having a blind date with Jun Han.
You said it felt like a blind date.
- With Jun Han.
- What?
- Yes. Jun Han.
- Don't bring that up.
You were too much.
How did you feel watching me go on a date with Jeong Won?
I didn't like it.
I try not to watch it.
But I can't help but watch it.
Jeong Won was doing what he had to,
so I have no hard feelings toward him.
I just have hard feelings on this person.
The part where Jeong Won and I were holding hands played,
and he suddenly went to the bathroom and didn't come out.
Jin Wu can be quite jealous.
I just didn't want to watch it.
I just watch it while laughing.
"Are you out of your mind?"
(Is he out of his mind?)
I can't watch it with a laugh.
Why did you do that back then?
I don't know. That was an AI.
- AI?
- That's so funny.
That wasn't me.
(Jin Young and Jeong Won quickly hit it off...)
(with their synergy.)
I'm planning to go into the cosmetics industry as well.
- It's because...
- You can ask me anything.
the ultimate goal of my business...
- is to get into cosmetics.
- Cosmetics?
It would be fun to make something together.
I'll help you a lot.
- Thank you.
- I like doing things with people.
- I'm a workaholic.
Me too. I always work...
I talked to Jin Young about work.
We were headed in a similar direction.
I felt attracted to her because of that.
"She's fun."
Our conversations were so interesting.
Goodness.
You're okay, right?
- Could you sit further away?
- Let's hold hands and watch.
Let's watch it while holding hands.
(Let's watch it while holding hands.)
(She held his hand as if she couldn't resist.)
It's really funny.
Whenever one couple is talking,
there's always another couple who gets physically affectionate.
- Really?
- Yes.
You have to watch them.
(Glancing)
(Holding hands)
(Looking around)
Seriously. I feel lonely.
I'll work up a little more courage.
- Right.
- I'll try to be a little braver.
You should fight for it.
- For you?
- Yes.
- Who...
- I'm trying...
- to fight for you.
- Goodness.
"I'm trying to fight for you?"
I don't know about this. That was also an AI.
I never said that.
It's a deepfake.
That's not me.
(The two confirmed their feelings for each other.)
Hold on. This is trouble.
I'm in real trouble.
Who did your hair today?
My hair?
(Speechless)
Guess who did it.
- I think it was you.
- What am I doing?
- Why am I doing that?
- I also have to trim my nails.
- Your nails are short.
- Right.
Would it hurt if I trim them more?
Please!
(Tilting her head)
That's...
(She's flustered.)
(She's ready to hit him.)
He's good at flirting with his hands.
No. That's not me.
- Can I say something?
- What is it?
Jeong Won held Jin Young's hand.
He didn't hold it like this.
It was like...
(It's so obvious that he's flirting.)
Right. He flirts like that.
Ji Hye.
You might be happy to hear this.
Jeong Won's ears don't blush...
when he's holding her hand,
but they do when he's talking to you.
That's because he's excited.
His ears became red.
I should also use my nails as an excuse of flirting.
You trim them until the white part doesn't show.
Well...
Come here.
- What?
- Look!
- Hold on.
- What did you talk about with her?
Hold on!
(She can't stand it.)
He...
Don't watch it.
Don't watch it! No, don't!
No.
- Come here.
- What?
What did you talk about with Ji Hye?
(The two naturally held hands.)
- How curious are you?
- These two are so fun.
I'm really curious. Tell me.
- Are you?
- Tell me.
(In a pinch)
Are...
(Walking on eggshells)
Get me some blood pressure medicine.
(Shocked)
What's that?
(Jin Young returned after talking to Jeong Won.)
Things must've gone well.
- Right?
- For sure.
- Yes, I'm in bliss. What do I do?
- Great.
A total bliss. What do I do?
(Unable to hide her feelings toward Jeong Won)
Are you okay?
I feel like I just got electrocuted.
(Jeong Won has dropped by Ji Hye and Jin Young's room.)
Hi.
What is it?
- I was just bored.
- Is that so?
- Do you want to go on a walk?
- Okay.
Wait. This is really bad.
What now?
- This is really bad.
- I want...
- a guy to drive me this time.
- Right?
If you could choose anyone to ride with,
choose me.
Should I get in right away?
- Yes, run and win me.
- Win you?
- Me?
- Yes, the passenger seat.
- It's your turn to win me now.
- What?
It's your turn to win me now.
I've used up too much of my energy so far.
- Your energy? You need to use more.
- Yes.
- More?
Do I need to try harder to win you over?
No, not really.
I'm going back inside.
(The conversation just kept going in circles and got them nowhere.)
I was actually...
on my way to see Ji Hye.
I've already talked to Jin Young a lot.
I went by Ji Hye's room hoping to talk to her...
a little more.
But Jin Young opened the door.
When she did,
she asked if I wanted to talk.
I couldn't reply with,
"No, I'm here to talk..."
"to someone else."
That's why I ended up talking to Jin Young.
- He was lying.
- It was a lie?
- Jeong Won is such a pro.
- He had gone over for Ji Hye.
Jeong Won was really mean.
I'm terribly sorry for lying,
but here's why.
Why did you do that? Seriously.
- He was lying.
- It was a lie?
- Jeong Won is such a pro.
- He had gone over for Ji Hye.
Jeong Won was really mean.
I'm terribly sorry for lying,
but here's why.
Why did you do that? Seriously.
I was indeed interested in Jin Young.
Believe me, it's the truth.
I even thought those feelings would get us somewhere.
Ji Hye kept saying she was interested in me,
but I couldn't tell.
Everything was all too chaotic for me.
As I had more fun being with Ji Hye...
and we didn't get to spend that much time at Yeon House,
my feelings did sway toward Ji Hye.
- And I still have feelings for her.
- Right?
That's what happened.
It was too long.
- My excuse was too long.
- Excuse?
- When...
- I'm sorry, Jin Young.
people are in a tough spot,
- they tend to make long excuses.
- Long excuses?
(I'm okay now.)
- Right?
- I agree with you.
(Jin Young and Jeong Won's last date)
- Who are you most comfortable with?
- What?
Among the girls.
- Comfortable with?
- Yes, not interest.
Simply who you're most comfortable with when chatting.
- The atmosphere has...
- Who do I feel...
- changed.
- comfortable chatting with?
- He'll probably say, "You." - "It's you."
When it comes to feeling comfortable,
it's Ji Hye.
(A close call)
What a relief.
What a great relief.
(Are you serious?)
How do I let him roam around freely from now on?
- Just how?
- Oh, dear.
My dad is going to be against me dating you now.
- At first...
- It's hot in here.
(Feeling hot)
I avoided asking you...
serious questions about...
- Ji Hye.
- I see.
I tried really hard to avoid it...
because asking you about her...
could've put great pressure on you.
(She held back from asking about Ji Hye.)
Maybe I was being conceited.
Things might've been different had I known...
- about it.
- Jin Young had...
a mental breakdown back then.
- Yes, she had a mental breakdown.
- She had a hard time back then.
To...
make you feel like...
you have another chance now is...
I don't want to do that.
(I don't want to make you feel like you have another chance.)
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
Oh, no.
I feel bad for Jin Young.
I no longer want to confuse you.
- Okay.
- That's how I feel.
(I no longer want to confuse you. That's how I feel.)
(Jeong Won and Jin Young have ended their relationship.)
All right.
Jeong Won made things clear back then.
- Really.
- For real, Jeong Won should...
apologize to Jin Young about this.
Jin Young cried quite a few times in front of me.
I comforted her every single time.
That's why...
I had no idea about Jin Young holding Jeong Won's hands...
or acting cute in front of him,
but I knew she had feelings for him.
(I knew she had feelings for him.)
I see.
(Yes.)
You have to leave while holding hands today.
Of course.
I'm giving her a piggyback ride.
(I'm giving her a piggyback ride.)
We're called the dopamine couple.
(Dopamine couple, Ji Hye and Jeong Won)
(Ji Hye and Jeong Won's first encounter)
Hi.
(Surprised)
My name is Kim Jeong Won.
- Kim Jeong Won.
I'd like to talk to Ji Hye first.
(I'd like to talk to Ji Hye first.)
Remember that scene?
Shall we go?
(Jeong Won chose Ji Hye.)
I'll be back.
I thought you had feelings for me.
(Because you chose me, I thought you had feelings for me.)
I did have feelings for you.
(I did have feelings for you.)
(1-on-1 Date, Jeong Won and Ji Hye)
This is a nice place.
I didn't think I'd have a meal under cherry blossoms.
Are you nervous?
- What was wrong with me?
- Oh, gosh.
A little bit. Maybe.
Really, what was wrong with me?
- Calm down.
- Okay, I will.
(Repulsed)
What you said just now...
It's the worst.
I thought you were bathed in butter.
For real.
Didn't that make your heart flutter? I bet you did.
I feel like throwing up watching that scene.
I teased him tons after the show.
I was like, "Are you nervous?"
Don't be, Jeong Won.
- I teased him tons.
- Gosh.
I'm dead nervous right now.
(During the pool party)
What was that?
You look like a lifeguard today.
Who really popped out back then was Ji Hye.
She was the definition of a hot girl.
(Jeong Won only had eyes for Ji Hye.)
(Following Ji Hye around)
Today was a lot of fun.
What was up with me back then?
He tried to look cool.
(Ji Hye had to hold hands with the guy...)
(she was most interested in.)
(Do you mind moving?)
Got it. Sit here.
My heart is beating fast.
(The two confirmed each other's feelings...)
Unbelievable.
(for the first time during the Truth Game.)
- Let's go.
- You trust me, right?
(They also had a retro date each other.)
We're turning?
You two had lots of fun.
Hold on.
(For Jeong Won who was scared)
Calm down.
(The two got closer during the scare.)
No, please.
That was how scared he was?
Those muscles aren't worth a thing.
Your hands are so sweaty.
Don't we look like a married couple if we pose like this?
(Ji Hye and Jeong Won expressed their feeling for each other.)
(However...)
I was most interested in you at first.
But it felt like you weren't interested in me.
So I thought, "She's just someone..."
"who isn't expressive."
But you kept saying you were certain.
"It's not me."
(Jeong Won thought Ji Hye wasn't interested in him.)
Really?
I'll go all in.
Oh, my.
The two are joined at the hip.
(Returning after the Day-drinking Date)
(Sliding)
- My gosh, holding hands again?
- Again?
Your hands are... Goodness.
Really, your hands.
(Ji Hye holds Jeong Won's hands like it's nothing.)
(Staring)
Are you certain now?
Yes.
You're the one for me.
(You're the one for me.)
Why were you two holding hands so much?
Jeong Won was...
What were you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about everything.
Ji Hye...
- I may be the obtuse type.
- Okay.
- Ji Hye...
- You're in an unfavorable spot.
No, listen.
I only found out Ji Hye expressed her interest in me...
while watching the show.
I found out while watching the show.
- Who didn't notice it?
- I didn't.
- I couldn't tell.
I knew,
so I embarrassed myself.
- See?
- Is that so?
You're a fox.
- Anyway.
- A fox.
(7 days later at the place Jeong Won and Ji Hye promised)
(Under the Lone Tree at the Olympic Park)
(Jeong Won arrived at the place first.)
(Will Ji Hye keep the promise from 7 days ago?)
(His mouth feels dry.)
(Turning)
(Smiling brightly)
Ji Hye looked gorgeous back then.
What's this?
(Ji Hye kept her promise with Jeong Won.)
(Happy)
- Let's hold hands.
- Let's go somewhere fancy.
Hands? Okay.
Fine. You two look good together.
- You do.
- Yes, they do.
While talking to you,
my ideal type slowly changed.
(Feeling happy)
What's with that smile?
I feel proud of myself.
My ideal type...
must've been someone...
I could enjoy life with.
That was in the back of my mind.
Let's get along well...
like we did in Yeon House...
- from now on.
- Okay.
You should've worn a wedding dress today.
I lacked finesse, right?
A little. This is nice.
Let's get along well.
There were many ups and downs.
- True.
- But you look great together.
- Thank you.
- It's...
She's right. You two look good together.
Are you exploding with dopamine even now?
- We're going strong.
- Yes, very strong.
- We're burning with love every day.
- For real.
We're going extremely strong.
Totally.
- It's kind of obvious.
- We have great chemistry.
Being together gives us so much joy.
- Exactly.
- You two look cute together.
We laugh so much when we're together that we've gained...
- so many new wrinkles.
- Is that so?
Let's go get Botox soon.
Okay.
Shouldn't they get it from you?
Must I give that couple Botox?
We're in your care.
Must I inject Botox into the wrinkles that formed...
from their happiness?
(Each other's relief pitcher, Jin Young and Jin Wu)
You have to leave.
How was the date?
I had lots of fun.
It was to the point where I lost track of time.
Would you be happy if I were to ask you out...
on a date again?
Yes. I'm serious.
(Ji Hye's answer makes his heart flutter.)
I'm serious, okay?
Honestly,
when I'm into someone,
all I do is make it obvious.
I don't know how to be sneaky about it.
Oh, gosh.
I'm the type to show my interest by making moves.
This is making me nervous for no reason.
(Jin Wu went all in on Ji Hye after the date.)
Like I don't know all about you,
you don't know all about me.
True.
I can make you laugh as well.
That's cute.
Isn't Jin Wu good with words?
I'm impressed by how good he is with words.
Jin Young must really...
- like sweet words.
- Right.
Do you not?
I...
No comment.
(A clear difference in taste)
I only ever complain about life when we're together.
He's such a puppy.
Jin Wu keeps following me around.
Complain about life?
Jin Wu was always within 3m of you.
- True.
- Right?
It was fun.
My favorite scene is about to play.
What is it?
Can I move three steps closer to you?
(Can I move three steps closer to you?)
Did you really say that, Jin Wu?
I don't remember.
(Embarrassed)
How cute.
Oh, my. Is it cute even though...
- He's cute.
- he's doing that to another girl?
I'm fangirling right now. I'm fangirling over Jin Wu.
Isn't he cute?
But smiling at her did upset me.
Why smile that much?
Especially at her, and not at me?
Something like that.
(That's cute.)
What do you want to talk about?
You know...
You said you were certain about someone.
I want to hear about that.
(Jin Wu wants to hear about Ji Hye's true feelings.)
I'm not...
the slow type or anything,
so I can kind of tell.
I'm not sure if you are guessing the right person.
(Thinking)
I'm not the one you're certain about, am I?
No.
- You're right about that.
- Right?
(Jin Wu has no place in Ji Hye's heart.)
Was that a good enough answer?
Was it?
(Nodding)
- Oh, no.
- This is breaking my heart.
- How upsetting.
- Right?
Goodnight.
I feel bad.
It was hard on me too.
Oh, no.
(It's breaking my heart.)
Jin Wu told me yesterday while watching the show together.
He had a real mental breakdown at that moment.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I'm really sorry, Jin Wu.
- Like, for real.
Even my younger sibling called me the worst after watching that scene.
"Ji Hye, you're the worst."
I was curious about this scene.
It's the end...
of Season One for me.
We are in Season Two, right?
Are you okay?
I'm just stating the facts. It's over for me.
Jin Young was a good listener.
- Yes.
- Right?
I'm not sure if I'm on the right track.
I felt really bad for him.
Although this is a show...
to get to know others and develop feelings for someone,
you don't have to force yourself to get to know someone...
or develop feelings for them...
when you don't have someone...
like that.
That's also for the sake of your date partner.
Wouldn't it be better to think,
"Let's just have some fun with whomever it is?"
That was... How do I put it?
It was a series of coincidences.
After being rejected by Ji Hye,
I was alone in the room.
I wanted to talk to someone, no matter who it was.
Just when I opened the door and stepped outside...
That was the first time...
I had an adult-like serious talk with Jin Young...
in those five days.
She was very different from the person I imagined.
That was the reason...
my feelings grew.
Jin Young was there...
like fate.
One thing led to another,
and I went on a date with her the next day.
That's fate.
Interesting, isn't it?
Tell me.
What did you two talk about?
- With Jeong Won?
- Yes. Tell me.
Up until last night, he gave me a clear indication...
of his feelings.
But after the date,
the two came back as if they were already a couple.
Right.
(Jin Wu moved next to the upset Jin Young.)
It could happen.
Right.
(Jin Young ended up crying in front of Jin Wu.)
The two cheered each other up a lot.
I want you to stop wasting your emotional energy on such things.
Why do you like someone who makes you cry?
"Like someone who makes you cry?"
- My bad.
- The shock...
has caused a mental breakdown.
- Is that so?
- I don't blame her for that.
Exactly.
Just use me as your emotional dumping ground.
Or go on a date with me to show off to him.
You don't have to see me ever again.
Just go on a date with me tomorrow. Please.
I want to take care of you, okay?
I don't want to give you false hope.
True. You're giving me false hope a lot of times.
Right? But I feel better after talking with you.
Talking makes you feel better.
- Totally.
- So don't cry, Jin Young.
(Jin Young feels better thanks to Jin Wu.)
I also agree with the fate part.
After being rejected by Jeong Won,
I was going through a total mental breakdown.
I didn't think I could handle it...
if I didn't talk about it to someone.
At that moment, Jin Wu was there.
Are you crying, Jin Young?
- It's making me emotional.
- Oh, dear.
- Don't cry.
- That's what happened.
(The past emotions make Jin Young tear up.)
It's okay.
Don't cry.
- It's okay.
- That's what happened.
You're fine now.
It's not that Jeong Won and Ji Hye did anything wrong.
I'm grateful.
In a way, that was what connected us,
and we're now a happy couple.
So are you two.
It's a happy ending.
- Right?
- That's what I think.
After watching that, I'm really grateful to Jin Wu.
I'd be too.
I'd be too. Watching you two made me teary as well.
- Right?
- It made me teary as well.
(Will Jin Young keep the promise from 7 days ago?)
I can't help but root for Jin Wu.
Right?
I've become a fan of Jin Wu.
- Jin Wu got teary at that moment.
- Hey.
I saw it.
(Smiling brightly)
It's like a love story.
(Jin Young rushes over to Jin Wu.)
Hey.
Were you waiting for me? Look at me. Are you crying?
(Shaking his head)
Were you waiting for me?
- Are you crying?
- No.
- You're not crying, are you?
- I'm not.
You look even better now.
You look handsome today.
What took you so long?
Were you waiting for a while?
(Sighing)
(They can't help but smile.)
Why am I smiling like I'm their mom?
- Me too.
- What's wrong with me?
It feels like I wasn't part of the show.
It's like I'm just watching it as an audience member.
Me too. I just feel like an audience member.
Jin Wu, I hope you're happy.
Thank you.
- I hope you're happy.
- Thanks to everyone's support.
(Thank you. I am, thanks to everyone's support.)
Why are you shaking so much?
Gosh.
He said he thought I wouldn't show up.
- He thought I wouldn't come.
- Really?
Can you hold my hand?
You look so pretty today.
- What? Do I look pretty today?
- You look pretty.
- I look pretty today?
- You do.
There was a lot I wanted to say to you.
(Smiling)
You've really thought this through over the past week.
Yes, you were all I could think about.
Really? To be honest,
I actually...
As I thought about it, I realized I felt comfortable with you.
Right.
And I appreciated how you took care of me.
I think I was moved by your consistency...
and how you always took care of me.
(They are what I like about you.)
- Is this really okay?
- You have to...
- Give her a peck.
You look so good. Give her a peck on the cheek.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
Your facial expression is different from last time.
- You have to marry me now.
- Gosh, I'm doomed.
You have no choice but to marry me now.
(An older woman and younger man couple with a 1-year age gap)
(Jin Wu and Jin Young are a couple.)
Those are so pretty.
After you officially became a couple, have your feelings...
or Jin Wu's actions changed in any way?
Jin Wu has gotten more affectionate.
He's very affectionate now.
He writes me a lot of letters.
Really?
- He handwrites them?
Yes, a lot of them are handwritten,
- and he texts me long messages too.
- Gosh.
- He texts you long messages?
- Yes.
(That's amazing.)
Jin Wu actually went on a trip to Japan...
not long after we became a couple.
He wrote me 5 letters so I could read 1 each day...
while he was gone for those five days.
From Monday to Saturday.
That way, I had one to read every day.
(That's amazing.)
Really?
(Jin Wu doesn't hold back when it comes to expressing his love.)
- That's amazing.
- How do you feel about that?
Really?
I'm not really into that.
(Ji Hye and Jin Wu are complete opposites.)
It's good we didn't end up together.
- Yes, you each found your person.
- Right.
I can't really read things like that.
(They're too cringey for me to read.)
You don't click "Read more" when a text is really long, right?
The words "View all" make me feel like I'm suffocating.
It's exhausting.
Gosh, I can't.
"Read more."
(That's understandable.)
It all worked out well.
That's why we don't text each other.
We video call instead.
We only talk over video calls.
Your KakaoTalk chat is probably just full of video call records.
Right, with no messages at all.
We only text each other about important things.
You two are a good match.
- Yes, everyone has their person.
- That's right.
(The older women and younger men each found their match.)
- It's our turn, Si Won.
- What?
- Gosh, this is going to be fun.
- Gosh.
- It's our turn, Si Won.
- What?
- Gosh, this is going to be fun.
- Gosh.
(Yu Jin and Si Won, the couple with a 12-year age gap)
- What number were you?
- My number?
In baseball, jersey numbers don't really matter,
but the player's position is related to the jersey number...
- in soccer.
- Yes, they're all different.
- The goalkeeper is number 1.
- Number 1.
And is the midfielder number 7?
- Is that right?
- Yes, but wingers get seven too.
- The wingers.
- You clicked so well that...
- you must have been attracted.
- Yes.
- I think that's when it started.
The waves are too rough.
(After playing in the water, the men gather around the women.)
Can't we do something about the waves?
I wonder if they can turn off the waves.
(Just then, Yu Jin got water on her face.)
(Watching carefully)
Right.
(Moving to sit in front of her)
- Sit.
- I'll act as your breakwater.
He's like a breakwater.
(Si Won shielded Yu Jin from the waves.)
- You shielded me from the waves.
- Yes.
I only found out about it when I watched the show.
(He expresses himself through actions rather than words.)
(Dinner time at Yeon House)
It's so...
- You should eat a lot and recharge.
- Yes.
- Right?
- But nothing sounds good.
Really?
If neither pizza nor chicken sounds good,
what should you eat?
- Porridge?
- Porridge.
I can use some instant rice to make porridge.
No, it's fine.
- I was really grateful at the time.
- It's...
The way you were by my side and...
I'll do it.
- You didn't look good at all.
- I was so sick.
I was so sick at the time.
(Si Won stayed by Yu Jin's side and took care of her.)
- Si Won is so caring.
- He is.
He takes good care of you in his own subtle way.
His affection is understated, unlike Jin Wu.
That's right.
Is Jin Wu's affection a little too cheesy for you?
No, Jin Wu is great.
Jin Wu is just really sweet.
His sweetness is a little cheesy?
(They're both caring, but in different ways.)
(It's time for the age reveal.)
- Si Won.
- It's Si Won.
Si Won is definitely young.
- Si Won is definitely young.
- Right.
- I think he's the youngest.
- I'm going to say 1999.
- Is he born in 2003?
- I was...
- born in 2002.
- Gosh.
- What age does that make you?
- If he's born in 2002...
I'm 25.
- You're 25?
- Yes.
I was born in 2002.
(Lowering their heads)
He's 25?
- That's shocking.
- You can't believe it?
No.
He's so calm.
I'm still reeling from the shock.
(Yu Jin is 12 years older than Si Won.)
Si Won, are you a Horse?
Yes. You're a horse too?
Yes. Goodness.
We're the same age, then.
(We're the same age, then.)
- Cheers.
(They all have a drink together after the age reveal.)
- We all saw it coming.
- Did you?
Cheers.
(Smiling)
He's so cute.
(Si Won is so cute.)
(Laughing)
- He's so cute.
- My face was so red.
(My face was so red.)
(These two still look good together.)
I didn't think the age reveal would be this early.
That's why...
I was worried about our 12-year age gap.
I was worried that the age gap...
would change how you feel.
What do you think?
You said you'd dated older women,
but they weren't that much older.
- It was five years, at most.
- Right.
What do you think about a 12-year age gap?
A 12-year age gap?
I don't think I'd rule someone out...
- because of their age.
- I see.
Even after you found out about the 12-year age gap,
were you attracted to each other?
Before the age reveal,
I actually wanted to talk to Yu Jin.
- Right.
- But the age reveal...
Still, I clicked the most with Yu Jin.
She made me feel comfortable during our time at Yeon House.
She listened to me a lot.
Whenever I talked to Si Won,
I didn't really notice the age difference.
- We had fun together.
- I saw clips of your dates.
Draw a heart on the palm of the person...
who was the most irresistible today.
(Draw a heart on the palm of the person...)
(who was the most irresistible today.)
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
Gosh, no.
(Which younger man was irresistible to Yu Jin today?)
Why did I volunteer to go first?
It would be nerve-racking to go first.
She keeps...
(Yu Jin chose Si Won.)
(Feeling shy)
They look so good with each other.
I'm shaking. Gosh.
I must be insane.
Just look natural for the photos like this.
- I like that.
- Right?
- Gosh, they look good together.
- They look good.
- This is much better.
- Yes.
- We look comfortable.
- You looked so good together.
(Gazing at Yu Jin)
This is good.
- Right?
- Yes, this is good.
Like this.
Si Won was so good-looking back then.
(Embarrassed)
(Putting his hand on her shoulder)
Goodness.
You put your hand on my shoulder?
- I did that?
- Right?
I can't believe you knew to do that.
(Reminiscing)
- What do you think?
- You look so pretty.
- That one's cute.
- It's cute?
You look good in it.
Are you only looking at me?
Yu Jin, you're quite good at flirting too.
(It's a little embarrassing,)
(but this was when their hearts fluttered the most at Yeon House.)
We had so much fun that day.
- Right.
- Yes.
I think I switched seats back then.
- I want to sit here, next to you.
- Okay.
(Si Won pushed Yun So to the side and left the corner seat empty.)
You were really proactive.
(Even during the job reveal)
That was kind of my usual spot.
- Yes.
- That's right.
(Si Won subtly left Yu Jin's usual spot open.)
- You always sat there.
- Yes.
- That's why.
- Really?
(Moved)
- I can't believe he did that.
- Right.
I didn't know about that.
Really?
Si Won, you're amazing.
Si Won would be a great husband.
- I always say that if I were...
- He's husband material.
just ten years younger, I would go for him.
He really is husband material.
(If I were just 10 years younger, I would go for him.)
(Their hearts are fluttering for Yu Jin.)
Really?
His plan worked.
(Hi!)
(Yu Jin's date)
Have you been waiting long?
I was so happy to see you, Si Won.
- Right.
- Seriously.
- I was happy to see you.
- Right?
I almost ran out to you.
(I was so happy to see you that I almost ran out to you.)
You should have.
Maybe I should've.
This place is so nice.
- It is.
- Right?
The air is nice and fresh.
- I should stay the night here.
- Right.
- Let's stay the night together.
- Okay.
- We have two days left.
- Yes.
Who would you go on a date with tomorrow?
Who else?
Who would you go on a date with?
For me,
there's this person called Choi Yu Jin.
(There's this person called Choi Yu Jin.)
Yes.
Si Won definitely seems like...
he's having more fun than he did with me.
(No argument there.)
No, Ji Hye. I had fun with you.
You're laughing a lot.
I do think that if I don't really notice the age gap...
during our dates, then it's fine.
That's why...
I want to see you outside of the show.
(That's why I want to see you outside of the show.)
Outside of the show?
- In reality. In our daily lives.
- In reality.
I want to hurry and see you outside.
- We should eat grilled hagfish.
Grilled hagfish?
Grilled hagfish is expensive.
- It's fine.
- It is?
(The two had looked forward to seeing each other outside.)
I was worried you wouldn't be here.
No way.
(Before they knew it, the final decision had arrived.)
Thanks to you, I had so much fun during our time here.
We should go get grilled hagfish right now.
(We should go get grilled hagfish.)
I was so nervous back then.
Okay.
(Yu Jin and Si Won chose each other for the final decision.)
- Let's go.
(As promised, Si Won arrives at the location first.)
Why is she taking so long?
(Glancing over at Si Won)
What happened to the grilled hagfish, Yu Jin?
(I'm sorry.)
(Yu Jin can't bring herself to watch.)
(Long after their agreed time,)
(Yu Jin still hasn't shown up.)
(Yu Jin couldn't keep her promise to meet 7 days later.)
(Yu Jin is unable to find the words out of guilt.)
Yu Jin,
if you'd shown up that day,
what would you have wanted to say to him?
If I'd shown up...
What would you have said to him?
If we'd met that day,
I think we would have talked about becoming a couple.
About how we would...
work as a couple.
What about you, Si Won?
I don't think I would have brought up marriage.
You don't think so?
- I think I would have.
- Oh, really?
The real-life things, like marriage.
Or, near the end, we talked about our friends.
- Right. We were worried about that.
- We were worried about...
Because of the age gap, we thought...
it might be awkward when we introduce each other to our friends.
We thought the age gap might become an issue...
when we meet each other's acquaintances.
I think we would have had a very real conversation.
Right.
(Maybe it's not too late for that.)
(Gosh)
You're fine.
(Jun Han, a.k.a. the flirting machine,)
(had a strong start but a weak finish.)
"Flirting machine" is too funny.
He really is a flirting machine, though.
Gosh, wait.
(I can't watch.)
Gosh.
(Jun Han was at the workout zone with zero Love QR votes.)
Look at you.
(He sets up the gym equipment with ease...)
(and begins working out.)
(Working out to shake off the hurt from the night before)
I don't let things shake my confidence.
If I show my serious side,
maybe I'll get a chance to redeem myself.
That's what I think.
(He's training his mind and body for a new mindset.)
Hong Seok Cheon said you should leave the show.
Hong Seok Cheon left a comment for you.
I know him personally.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Amazed)
You two know each other?
Did he contact you?
Seok Cheon and I...
filmed a video for Instagram in the past.
We've eaten meals together too.
Seok Cheon and I are close.
Wait.
I'm into women.
- I didn't say anything.
- No one doubts that.
Nobody here doubts that.
I almost got the wrong idea.
(Day 2, Jun Han is checking his Love QR Code.)
I feel like I got zero votes again.
(Turning his phone away)
All right.
(Did he get any Love QR messages from the older women?)
Do you see that?
What?
(You have received four Love QR messages.)
That was a touching moment.
Jun Han is adorable.
Right. You were full of charm, Jun Han.
I couldn't believe it.
It felt like a dream.
Last night, I was in shock.
Today feels like a dream come true.
- That's understandable.
- Right.
(He's celebrating going from 0 votes to 4 votes.)
I was so touched back then.
He's like a big kid.
- He is.
- Right.
(Jun Han has an innocent, boyish charm.)
(Jun Han and Yu Jin's 1st-come, 1st-served date)
- I thought he was insane back then.
- I'll do it for you.
- Me too.
- Originally...
- Do you know that?
- What?
During a date,
princesses shouldn't have to lift a finger.
(Speaking tactfully)
- Gosh.
- I am feeling shy, so I'll...
My friends teased me so much for that.
It's so pretty.
(The sunset is so pretty.)
(Hesitating)
You're pretty too, Jin Young.
(You're pretty too, Jin Young.)
(Everyone is stunned.)
Gosh, that's awful.
I thought he only acted like that with me.
I should watch and learn.
(Jun Han and Ju Hee's overnight date)
You really got to me.
(You really got to me.)
He said, "You really got to me."
(Shocked)
(Unable to keep a straight face)
(Stunned)
All I can do is clap.
(He has accepted his fate.)
- Gosh.
- What?
You're blinding me.
Can you turn down that halo?
- What?
- Your halo is blinding me.
No, I chose you for the First Impression Vote.
- Really?
- Yes.
You can't do this to me right now.
You're giving me a dopamine rush.
I really do catch feelings way too fast.
You can see the question mark on my face.
Gosh.
You're my dopamine rush.
(You're my dopamine rush.)
(Jun Han's flirting is dizzying.)
You're my dopamine rush.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Jun Han was...
Each of the older women did choose Jun Han at least once.
Jun Han was chosen.
- He was chosen by us.
- You're right.
All Jun Han did was go along with it,
but everyone saw him as a flirt.
That's right. Everyone rejected me.
Did you lie when you said you've only dated older women?
No.
- Why? Does he seem awkward?
- He does.
I just felt rushed during that time.
That's understandable.
Who left the biggest impression on you?
And what moment?
For me,
I had the most fun when I had drinks with Ji Hye.
That moment...
was so fun to me and I felt like we clicked.
I think that's why Ji Hye was my final decision.
(Their time at Yeon House is now a fond memory.)
(Revealing the real couples still together today)
I feel like I'm taking a puppy home.
So cute.
(Winking)
So cute!
(I love this.)
He's so cute.
(Jin Young's puppy, Jin Wu)
You're so cute together.
I came here to find love,
and I'm leaving with the person I fell for.
You look like high school students.
Yun So and I have...
an 11-year age gap.
We'll just have to make it work.
(We'll just have to make it work.)
- Our age gap.
- Our age gap?
We can overcome it, right?
I really like you.
(I really like you.)
After meeting you,
I broke all stereotypes based on age.
You're a shorty.
(Pressing)
(Finding her cute)
(Walking, running)
Why is this so funny?
- This is so funny.
- I really want to punch you.
You're someone who helped me realize...
that age doesn't matter.
That's cute.
- I mean it.
- No!
(I mean it.)
I feel so happy right now.
I believe things will get even better.
Everyone looks so adorable.
I'll do my best for an exciting relationship.
(Come here.)
(Are you ready?)
(Charging forward)
That's cute.
(Come at me.)
Stop!
(Ji Hye charges forward as well.)
(Running away)
I've made memories...
and left after finding my partner.
It was a meaningful time.
(It was a meaningful time in the Yeon House.)
(Three couples of older women and younger men were made...)
(with age differences of 1, 6, and 11.)
Starting without knowing each other's jobs and ages...
felt very significant.
It's a place I would strongly recommend...
for those who want to meet people without any titles or biases.
This isn't a place for unserious relationships...
just because it's a dating show.
This is a place...
where I found my lover I thought I would never find...
in my life.
I think it will be a great place for those...
who want to be in a serious relationship.
I strongly recommend the Yeon House...
for those who want to abandon any stereotypes...
based on love and age.